campsaver.com 2016-11-08

# Privacy & Security :: CampSaver.com

## Privacy Statement

 **We value and respect the privacy of all our user guests** and want you to know how we handle information we learn about you when you visit our Web site or make a purchase. The provisions of this notice will apply to current customers as well as former customers unless we indicate otherwise.

Because we value our customers, we will provide any information our guests request about the information we have collected about them. By request we will erase any information that our guests do nor want us to maintain. All employees at Camp Saver LLC are required to keep personal data of our guests and customers confidential. The Camp Saver LLC web site uses secure server transactions and follows federal regulations to collect personal data.

## Data Collection

### Credit Card Data

We do not store credit card numbers on our website. We require our customers to enter their credit card details on every purchase in order to protect your personal data

### Non-personal Data Collected

Guests may browse our site without disclosing any personal data. The following non personal data will be collected though:

  * your domain name and the date and time you accessed our site
  * the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site

We use this data to analyze the effectiveness of the site and better serve our guests.

### Personal Data Collected

Our guest users may browse our site without disclosing any personal information. The only personal information we collect is that which you choose to provide to us. Other personal Information including but not limited to: Name, address, phone number, age, gender, credit card, shipping address, may be collected if you choose to provide it. We do not sell, rent, lease or give your personal information to any third-party organizations or anyone for that matter. This information will be used for:

  * shipping orders, sending information, answering questions, processing orders.
  * data mining.

### Third-Party Disclosure

We do not disclose personal data to any third-party organizations.

### Children

We do not knowingly collect any information from children.

## Email

We do not sell, rent, lease or give your email to any third-party organizations. We do not send unsolicited email. **We do not spam**. If you choose to provide us with your email address we will use it to send:

  * answers to questions and/or requested information, order confirmations, and receipts.
  * newsletters, product announcements and/or special promotions.

If you have opted to receive promotional email from Camp Saver LLC and later decide to opt out of our email list you may do so by clicking here or click the Unsubscribe link found at the bottom of any promotional email we send you. We will then remove your email from our database.

## Support

If you have any questions regarding the Camp Saver LLC Privacy Policy, please contact us.
